gyanbook.in 2018-08-31

# PRIVACY POLICY - GyanBook

**Privacy Policy for Http://gyanbook.in**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at vikashprashantbittu@gmail.com

At  **Gyanbook** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by  **www.GYANBOOK.in**  and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites,  **Gyanbook**  makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
**Gyanbook**  does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or customise Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  **www.GYANBOOK.in**  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to  **Gyanbook.net**  and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  **Gyanbook** ‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
